（梓）ふんふふふんふん。
（山村）お～。
おほ～！
Oh!
St. Ishiyama School Festival
ヤキソバうまいよ～。
さあ　どうぞ　ヤキソバ。
Tasty Yakisoba right here!
Here's Dance Heaven! Thanks for waiting!
（呼び込みの声）
Come shop here!
See the Cosplay show!
Test your courage in the Haunted House!
うえへへ！やっぱり
中学の文化祭とは違うね～。
It sure is different from
our middle school festivals!
すっごいすっご～い！うふふ！
Amazing! Just amazing!
＜みなさん　こんにちは　もう
覚えてないかもしれないけど→
Hello everyone.
You probably don't remember me,
男鹿さんの弟子の
山村和也です＞
but I am Oga-san's disciple, Yamamura Kazuya.
＜ということで我が学園の
学園祭が始まったワケですが＞
And as you can see, our school
festival has already begun.
（梓）カズくん！
（山村）あ？
Kazu-kun!
梓　メイドやります！
I, Azusa, shall be a maid!
へ？
（３人）お帰りなさいませ！
ご主人さま！
Welcome back, Master!
（友人）
５番テーブル　アイスコーヒー
入りま～す。
Maid Café
Iced Coffee is ready for Table 5!
（梓）は～い！
（友人）メイド喫茶やってま～す。
Okay!
Come to our Maid Café!
（友人）ねえねえ　思ったほど
お客さん　来てなくない？
Hey, don't you think business
is slower than we expected?
そお？
You think so?
ん～まだ始まったばっかりだし
これからこれから！
Well, we only just opened.
The crowds will come!
そうだね。
（ベル坊）ダーブ！
You're right.
（山村）あ～。
どうしたの？カズくん。
元気ないね～。
What's the matter, Kazu-kun?
Where's your spirit?
学園祭だよ～！アゲアゲで
行こうぜ！アゲアゲ～！
It's the school festival! We gotta
prance and romp and romp and prance!
俺は今　悩んでんだよ。
なんで？
Right now, I'm a man with worries.
What about?
オレだって一応は
男鹿さんの弟分なんだぜ。
You know that I am Oga's sworn
little brother... more or less.
昨日の放課後　バレーの練習を
手伝おうと体育館に行ったら…。
But yesterday after school,
when I went to the gym to help
him practice for volleyball...
（飛鳥）
((あ～？何ジロジロ見てんだよ))
Huh? What're you staring at here?!
（由加）
((テメ…セントの人間だなぁ？))
You're a St. Ishiyama brat, right?
((立ち入り禁止だ　ゴラァ))
This place is off limits to you!
((敵状視察かぁ？))
((オニぶっつぶすぞ　オラァ))
You're an enemy spy?
You are gonna get so creamed!
（２人）((ああん！？))
レッドテイルの姉ちゃんたち
すんげ～怖くて→
Those Red Tail girls just scare me!
スゴスゴと　しっぽ巻いて
逃げてきたんだね！
So you came running back with
your tail between your legs?
う！ズバリ言うなよ！
Show some tact!
え？じゃあ　負け犬！？
よけいワリィだろ！
Then... you're a beaten dog?
That's even worse!
はい　そこの人～ジャマジャマ～。
Hey, Mister. Shove off!
あ？
手伝わないんなら
どっか行ってよね。しっしっ。
Huh?
If you're not going to help, then
take it elsewhere! Shoo! Shoo!
うっうう…あうあう！
あっ逃げた。
にゃははは！
ホントにワンコみた～い。
Oh, he ran off.
He really did run like a doggy!
ガチで負け犬だね。
ねっ。
He seriously is a beaten dog!
Maids Run Amok
Morning Schedule: 10:00 K-on Club Concert
Afternoon Schedule: 1:30 Volleyball Match Finals
（邦枝）遅い！ん～。
They're late!
（寧々）
まあ～試合は午後からですし。
Maybe, but the game's not
until the afternoon, and...
Annoyed Annoyed
そうは言っても！
作戦会議とかあるんだから！
That's no excuse! We have pre-game
strategy meetings and such!
（千秋）うんうん。
大体この試合で負けたら
退学なのに→
I mean, if we lose this
game, we're all expelled!
みんな緊張感が。
そんなワケじゃ…。
Nobody's the least bit anxious!
That isn't true...
（由加）葵姐さ～ん！
（一同）ん？
Madam Aoi!
ユニフォーム出来たっす！
なんとか間に合いました。
Ishiyama Sports
The uniforms are like all made!
Somehow they came in under the wire.
おつかれさま！で　どんなの？
Nice going. So what do they look like?
姐さんのは　これっす！
ブー！
Madam, this one's yours!
Isn't that just a swim suit?
ただの水着やん。
イエス！
Yes!
えと　それより
他のメンバーは？
Um... Whatever. What about the guys?
ああ　神崎先輩と姫川先輩とは→
Ah. We just passed Kanzaki-sempai
and Himekawa-sempai.
さっき　すれ違ったっすけど
時間まで　うろついてるって。
They say they're going to
hang out until game time.
はあ？じゃ　男鹿と東条は！？
２人とも　まだみたいですね。
Huh? Then what about Oga and Tojo?
Haven't seen anything of either one of them.
それじゃ古市くんは！？
Then what about Furuichi-kun?!
（由加）姐さん！
あっいた？
Madam!
Oh? He's here?
もったいないんで
着てみたっす！
It shouldn't go to waste,
so I'm trying it on!
うが～。
時々あんたを尊敬するよ。
ナイス！
There are times when I respect you.
Nice!
そ　そんなもんいいから！
古市君だけでも探してきなさい！
Enough of all that! Get out there
and at least find Furuichi-kun!
（古市）
ハッハッハッハー来ましたよ！
Here I am!
わ～！智将が来てくれた～。
Master Strategist is here!
いや～かわいい同級生が
メイド喫茶　始めたと聞いて→
Well, when I heard the cute girls from my
graduating year were doing a Maid café,
いても立っても
いられなくってね～。
I couldn't stay away!
でもバレーの試合の方は
大丈夫なんですか？
But don't you have a volleyball
game? Should you be here?
ああ　そっちは
俺の授けた秘策があるから。
Sure! They already have
my brilliant game plan!
大丈夫さ。
わ～すご～い！さすが智将！
Have no fear!
Cool! Just like a strategist!
ふふん　それではメイド喫茶の
イロハを見せていただこうかな。
And thus, perhaps you can show
me the pleasures of a maid café!
がってんだ！
Agreed!
くぅ～切ない！
（生徒たち）キャー！
I... hurt!
わ～！
（ドドド…）
う　うう…。
なんだあ？
What the...
（七海）いらっしゃいませ。
（アレックス）ようこそ　当店へ。
I bid you welcome...
...to our shop.
（榊）歓迎…。
Our pleasure.
（生徒たち）キャー！
六騎聖の人って　もう少し
怖いのかと思ってたけど。
I would have thought that the Six
Holy Knights would be scarier!
紳士的でステキ～。
They're so elegant and wonderful!
イケメン最高～。
And oh-so handsome!
静御前も美しすぎる～。
たまら～ん。
Shizuka is just too beautiful
like Shizuka Gozen!
Almost unbearable!
キャー。
六騎聖が喫茶店を！？
The Six Holy Knights are
running a coffee shop?
♪～　ふふふん～
（山村）梓いるか～！？
Is Azusa here?
お？あっワンコ帰ってきた！
俺は犬じゃねえっての！
Oh! The doggy is back!
Hey, I'm not a dog!
そんな事より梓　大変だぞ。
But enough about that!
You've got trouble, Azusa!
こっちの客の入りが悪いのは
六騎聖のやってる→
You're not getting customers,
because the Six Holy Knights have
opened a gorgeous, trendy coffee shop,
ゴージャスでセレブな喫茶店に
人が流れてるせいなんだ！
and everybody's there!
なんとぉ！
（古市）なるほどな。
What?!
Of course!
は？
だが　しかし　それだけではない。
But even so...
That is not all.
あっ古市さん
いらしてたんですか？
Furuichi-san, you're here too?
それだけではないって　いったい！？
But when you say, "That is
not all," what do you mean?
この店の接客態度　内装　メニュー
一通り見せてもらったが…。
I have experienced this shop's welcoming
atmosphere, interior design, menu, all aspects...
すべてダメだ！
...and find it wanting!
お～。
てゆ～か。
何なの？この人。
Wait a sec.
What's the deal with this jerk?
そこの２人！
（友人たち）はいぃ！
You two!
Yes, Sir?
せっかくの学園祭だというのに
このまま人気のない→
This is your only school festival all year!
Do you want it to end as an impoverished,
customer-less maid café failure? Huh?!
うらぶれた喫茶店で
終わっていいのかね？
ん～！？
いや…それは…。
さすがに困るけど。
N-No, I...
I wouldn't, but...
でしょお～！
（友人たち）ハイィ！
Yes, Sir!
メイド喫茶の酸いも甘いも
かみわけた→
I know all the ins and outs of maid cafés!
この俺の言う通りに
やってみたまえ！
Therefore do precisely as I say!
（一同）おお～！
《あの智将古市が
本気に！すげえ》
Furuichi the Strategist is deadly serious!
This is great! He's going to spar with the
Six Holy Knights even before the volleyball game!
《バレーの前に六騎聖との
前哨戦だぜ！》
Lesson 1: Greetings
ということで
まずはアイサツからだ。
And so first, we start with
how you greet your customers.
いきなり言われてもぉ～。
We can't do it just like that!
とりあえず　お手本
見せてくださいよ～。
（友人たち）ね～。
All right, then give us a sample.
Right?
ん～お手本か…。
Hm. A sample...
（アランドロン）おかえりなさいませ～
ご主人さまぁ。
Welcome back, Master!
そう！これだよ　これ！な！
Yes! That's exactly right, Miss...
（４人）ギャー！
そこで何やってんだよ！
What are you doing there?!
ええ～大事なご主人さまの
古市殿が→
Well, I heard that my beloved Master
Furuichi was in the market for a sweet little maid!
かわいいメイドを
ご所望とききまして～。
はせ参じた次第なのです～。
And this was the only place for me!
うふっ。
うわあああ！なんじゃこりゃ！
What's that supposed t' be?!
でい！
ぎゃあああ！
な　何ですか？君たちは！
Who are you guys?!
てめえの店のたこ焼き
中がドロドロで生焼けだろうが！
The takoyaki from your stand
is runny and undercooked!
それは京風たこ焼きだから
トロトロで…。
But Kyoto-style takoyaki
is always chewy and juicy!
キョウフウも　タイフウもあっか！
Never heard of no Komodo-style!
しかもな！歯に青のり
くっついて→
And look! It's got seaweed
sprinkles stuck to my teeth!
こんなんなっちまったぞ！
This is how my teeth look now!
ああ！？
わぁ！すみませ～ん！
Ahh! I'm so sorry!
…てえことで料金はタダな！？
はい～。
So our takoyaki is free today, right?
Yes, Sir.
あ～ん…。
やっぱ坊っちゃん嬢ちゃん
高校だなぁ。
As we thought! A school
of spoiled rich brats!
チョロイもんだぜ！
さ～て～次は何を→
They're pushovers!
So... What are we going to get for free next?
タダ食いさせてもらおうかな。ん？
（女生徒）
メイド喫茶いかがですか～？
メイド喫茶やってま～す！
Would you like to try a maid café?
We have a maid café open today!
おう　姉ちゃん。
あ？
Hey, Missy!
１枚よこせや。
ひいい！
Hand over one of them fliers!
あ　ああ…。
かわいいメイド喫茶～？
"Cute Maid Café"?
楽しそうじゃねえか！
Sounds like fun to me!
よ～し！いっちょ
食後のお楽しみと　しゃれこむか！
Right! First we get maids to serve us
snacks, then they're our main course!
（一同）おう！
ダーブ！
というわけでメイド喫茶名物
オムライスの名前書き出来たか？
And so...
Have we cooked our Maid Café Specialty:
omelet-rice with the customer's name in ketchup?
（友人たち）ん～。
こんなんやって
なんか意味あんの？
I don't get it! What's the
reason for doing this?
だいたい私たち　ちょっとメイドの
コスプレしてみたかっただけだし。
I mean, the only reason we're doing this is
because we wanted to cosplay as maids a bit.
（アランドロン）できました～！
（友人たち）ん？
Mine is finished!
いかがですか？古市ご主人さま。
How do you like mine, Master Furuichi-sama?
おお！見事な智将のケチャ文字！
Oh! A perfectly written,
"Strategist"! ("Chishou")
そうそう！これだよ　これ！
Yes! Yes! This is exactly it!
おほめくださり
ありがとうございます～。
May I thank you for your words of praise?
古市ご主人さま　キラッ！
Master Furuichi-sama!
Twinkle!
（古市）
《ダメだ…使い物になるのが
このオッサンだけとは》
This is terrible! The only one
with skills is this old man!
梓も出来ましたぁ！
Azusa made one too!
あ？
Disgrace ("Chishou")
バンザーイ！バンザーイ！
ちしょ～イエーイ！
Banzai! Banzai! Strategist!
《梓…あんた…》
（友人）
《天然って怖ぇ～》
（山村）
Azusa, You're...
Airheads can be scary!
いや～まあ　なんだ　オムライスは
この辺にして　お次は～。
Yes, well, um... Let's leave
the omelet-rice there. Next...
（邦枝）お次は何かしら～？
はうあ！
Yes, what do we have next?
人が　さっきから待ってれば
こんなところで！
You keep me waiting, and
here is where I find you!
違うんです！クイーン！
これにはワケが！
You have it wrong, Queen! I have my reasons!
そ　そう！
バレーボール対決の前に→
Y-Yes, the volleyball match hasn't started,
すでに六騎聖との戦いは
始まっているんですよ！
but the battle with the Six
Holy Knights has already begun!
は？
前哨戦とはいえ→
Sure, it's just a preliminary bout,
but we mustn't back down here!
ここは負けるワケには
行きません！
今回は　あの男鹿だって
本気なんですから！
And Oga... He's very serious about it!
うっ！男鹿が本気！？
Oga's serious?
（男鹿）((うりゃ～！))
（邦枝）《まさか→
Could it be that the entire
reason Oga was all beat up
昨日ボロボロだったのは
秘密特訓のせい！？》
was due to his strenuous special training?!
((ガオオオ))
《だったら私も
ここで逃げ出すわけには…》
If so, then I mustn't back
down from this fight here!
そうでしょ？クイーン。
わかったわ！→
You see my point, Queen?
Count me in! So what do we have to
do to defeat the Six Holy Knights?!
で　六騎聖に勝つには
何をすればいいの！？
それは…はい！
ん？
You will need... This!
ささ！これを。
Yes! Simply put this on!
え？
さ～て。
ダーブ！
And now...
いよいよか！腕が鳴るぜ！
マダ！
Finally! I hunger for action!
（グー）
そして腹も鳴るぜ！
And I hunger for food!
アダ！
昨日　暴れすぎたからな～。
I just went overboard yesterday.
バレーの試合の前に
まずは腹ごしらえだ。
Before we do any volleyball, we need
to fortify ourselves with good eats!
ダーブダ！
ウイーッス！お好み焼きくれ～。
ダブウ～。
Yo! Fire up an okonomiyaki for me!
（東条）へい　らっしゃい。
あ？
Welcome t' the shop!
（東条・男鹿）あ～！？
ア～ウ？
Maid Café Right Here!
ほら　ここっすよ。
See? It's right here!
メイド喫茶ね　たしかに
あいつが　いそうだわ。
A maid café? Yeah, I'd
expect to find him here!
ここにいるのは
わかってんだよ！え…。
We already know you're in
here, so you'd better...
W-Welcome back, Master!
お…お帰りなさいませ～
ご主人様。
（寧々）ねえさん…。
Madam...
あ！イヤー！見ないで
ご主人様～！
Oh, no! Please don't look, Master!
（由加）何やってんすか？
What are you doing?
だってえ　六騎聖との
前哨戦だっていうからぁ…。
I know, but... He said it was a preliminary
bout with the Six Holy Knights...
（千秋）《かわいい》
Cute!
なるほど！水着じゃなくて
メイド服のユニフォームなら→
I get it! You didn't want the swim suit
because you wanted a maid uniform instead!
良かったんすねぇ～！そうじゃなくて！
Not even close!
（古市）や～　君たち！
Yo, ladies.
（寧々）やっぱいたか…。
I knew he'd be here.
Are you ladies interested in battling
the Six Holy Knights as well?
君たちも　クイーンと一緒に
六騎聖と戦ってみないか？
（寧々）ハァ？
Shall we?
さあ…。
Executive Café
さて　そろそろ
試合の準備をしないとね。
Now then...
It's about time to prepare for the match.
まだ　いいんじゃないですか？
I see no reason to hurry.
After all, our win is assured.
どうせ勝つのは
我々に決まってますし。
ま　そうね。
Yes, that's true.
（ガラスが割れる音）
あ！ううっ…。
What is the trouble?
（七海）何の　さわぎ？
帝毛工業の生徒に　うちの
たこ焼きの屋台→
The students from Teimo Tech
broke up my takoyaki stand!
めちゃくちゃにされた上に
食い逃げまでされて…。
They even ran off without
paying for their food!
何ですって！？
（生徒）≪どうか　お助けを～！→
What was that?!
Please, come save me!
うわ～ん　うわ～ん…≫また帝毛ですか。やれやれです。
Teimo Tech again? What'll we do with them?
フッ…私たちの出番みたいね。
It seems our time has come.
（古市・山村）ん～…。
智将　これは？
Strategist, is this...
うむ…。
I said, what the hell are you here for?!
何しに来たっつってんだよ！
あの～　２人なんだけど。
Um, the two of us...
（寧々）あぁ？２人だから何だっつ～の！
What about the two of you?!
（客達）ひぃ～！
いや～　その→
Nothing... Just that we were hoping for
you to say, "Welcome back, Master."
ご主人様　お帰りなさい的な
ごあいさつとか　その…。
ああん？誰が　いつ　おめえらの
舎弟になったんだよ！！
When did I ever rank lower
than you two creeps?!
（客達）あぁ～…すんませ～ん！
We're so sorry!
何　頼むッスか？
So what is it ya want?!
はよ言え　オラ。
Hurry up and decide!
Um... Um... How about your, "100% Love
Infused Hand-Squeezed Orange Juice?
えっと　それじゃあ　この
「ラブ１００％注入　手作り→
オレンジジュース」ってのを…。
ホレ。
Here.
は？
飲め。
飲めや。
Drink!
Drink it!
で　でも…。えっ！
B-But...
え～…。
わ…わ～い　いただきま～す！
S-Sure! I'm drinking it down now!
（男子達）ギャー！
待って～！待って　待って！
Wait up! Stop! Wait for me!
（男子達）ギャー！
ご主人様　ご主人様　待って～！
Oh, Master!
Oh, please, Master! Wait for me!
やっぱり　私のほんとのご主人様は古市殿だけって事なのかしら？
Yes, as I thought, my true one-and-only
Master must be Furuichi-dono!
ウフッ！待ってえ～！
Oh, wait!
((と　とんでもない計算違い
だった。このままじゃ…))
This is one of the worst mistakes
in my career! If this goes on...
またまたご主人様
いらっしゃいました～！
And yet another Master has arrived!
は　は～い！お帰りなさいませ
ご主人さ…ま。
Yes! Welcome back, Mas...ter?
（ヒルダ）フム…そうだな。
Ah, yes...
あのぉ…。
Uhh...
この「かわいいパティシエール手作りの
夢色パンナコッタ」というのを貰おうか。
I shall eat this, "Cute Patissiere's
Hand-Made Yumeiro Panna Cotta."
へい！よろこんで！
Yes! With pleasure!
（梓）パンナ一丁！
≪パンナ入りま～す！≫
One Panna, coming up!
One Panna, all ready!
（古市）ヒルダさぁ～ん！
Hilde-san!
ん？何だ　ウザ市か。
If it isn't Annoyichi?
助けてくださぁ～い！
Please rescue me!
助けろだと？
はい。この服を着て→
"Rescue," you say?
Yes! I'm begging you to wear
this and help out the café!
店を手伝ってほしいんですぅ！
ほぉ…。
人間界では　メイドの中でも
より位の高い者を　レディースメイド→
There is no position higher in the world
of maids than that of the Lady's Maid!
すなわち　侍女と呼んだという…。
Otherwise known as the "Lady in Waiting"!
は？豆知識ですか？
Huh? A bit of trivia?
よかろう！主に仕えるとは
どういうことか→
Fine! You want to know what, "service
to one's Master," truly means?
この侍女悪魔の私が
ビシバシ叩きこんでやろう！
This Demon in Waiting shall
beat that lesson into you!
え？あ　その…。
Eh? Ah... Um...
（東条）はっ！
（東条）はい。
Hey.
で　どうなんだ？
Well? What do you think?
何がだ？あ　次ブタ玉。
Think about what? Next, I want
the Pork & Extra Egg Special.
（東条）はい。
Here.
（東条）勝てる見込みは立ったの
かって　聞いてんだよ。
I'm asking if we're predicted to win!
フフ…あ　次ミックス。
Next, I want the Mixed Special.
（東条）はい。
Here.
ま　午後の試合を
楽しみにしときな。
All I can say is just you
wait for our afternoon match.
あ　次イカ玉。
（東条）はい。
Ah! Next a Squid Spe...
Here!
フフフ…。
すげえ　１２枚目いったぞ！
Amazing! He's gone 12 plates so far!
たった３分で　１２枚の
お好み焼きを…バケモノか！？
H-How can a human eat 12
okonomiyaki in three minutes?!
Is he a monster?
はい　次　明太もち！
（東条）はい！
Next, one with pollock roe!
Here!
で　そのメイド喫茶ってのは
どこなんだ？
So...? Where's this Maid
Café supposed to be?
この辺の教室な
はずなんだが…。
It'd be in a classroom right in this area...
何だよ　あのメイド喫茶…。
おそろし過ぎるぅ。
What is with that maid café?!
Nothing should be that scary!
（３人）あ？
さ～　いらはい！いらはい！
≪あそこか！≫
Yes! Come on in! Come on in!
Over there, huh?
ヘヘ…かわいいメイドさんに
ヨロシクしてもらいましょうかね。
We'll go let the cute
maids treat us like kings!
そうだな。
Count me in!
Eight Masters, weary from their
journey, are in the house!
遠路はるばる　８名の
ご主人様　ご来店～！
（一同）え？
（メイド達）お帰りなさいませ
ご主人様。
Welcome back, Master.
ここ　ほんとにメイド喫茶かよ？
Is this really a maid café?!
ちょっと豪華すぎねえか？
ま　まあ　いいじゃねえか。
Looks way too pricey...
Y-Yeah, but what the hell? We'll
just make sure we have fun our way!
オレたちなりに
楽しませてもらおうぜ。
ダブ　ダー！
≪おい　そこのメイド！≫
は？あっしっスか？
Hey, you maid over there!
Huh? Ya mean me?
そうだ。写真とらせろ。
Right! We're takin' pictures!
しかも　ただの写真じゃねえ。
ちょっとムフフな写真をな…。
But we don't mean just any kinda picture!
We mean the kinda picture that
makes guys say, "Mu ha ha"!
あ～　いいっすよ～。
Yeah, why not?
ほぉ。
ききわけが　いいじゃねえか。
Now that's a gal who knows what I want!
さあ　とらせろ！
（アランドロン）は～い！→
Let's get that shot!
Okay!
You're free to take any picture from
any angle that your heart desires!
さあ　どんなアングルでも　お好きな
写真を　とって下さいませ～。
（ザコ達）う～～！！
Don't give us that kinda crap!
いいかげんにしろぉ！
何だ　このキモい　メイド喫茶は！
What kind of creepy maid café is this?!
かまわねぇ
ぶっこわしちまえ！
オウ！
Do your worst! Take this place apart!
ゲス共が…。
Worthless trash!
どうやら貴様らも　他の客同様
我々の使えるべき→
It seems you are just like
all of the other customers.
You are not masters fit for our service!
主では　なかったようだな。
ああん！？
ご主人様に何て口のききかただ！
What kind of talk is that
to say to your Master?!
よかろう。ならば
最高の土産をくれてやる。
Fine! Then I shall gift you with
the world's greatest present!
お？やっとサービスしてくれる
気になったか？
Oh? You're finally going to give
us the service we deserve?!
ただし…冥土の土産だがな。
But be aware! This present
is made in the underworld!
（ザコ達）え？
（寧々）オラ　やっちまえ～！
All right, get 'em!
≪あっ！≫≪ウッ！≫
≪ブサイクが！≫
（殴る音）
≪オラ！≫≪ウッ！≫
アウー。
（ザコ達）ヒィヒィ…。
何もんだよ　あいつら…ウッ！
Who were those people?!
てめえ気をつけ…あ！
You bastard, watch where you're...
（神崎）ああん？
（夏目）何　こいつら？
Just who is this?
（姫川）
誰に向かって
もの言っちゃってんのかな～？
Now who were those rude words directed at?
お　お前ら…。
石矢魔の東邦神姫！？
It's you!
Ishiyama's TKKH!
ダブルかかと落としくらうか？
あぁ？
Do you want a Double Heel Kick?
試合前の肩ならしに
ちょうどいいかもね～。
だな。
It may be the perfect way to
warm up just before a match.
True.
やべえ！
This is bad!
クソッ！ウッ！
Damn it!
バカヤロウ　じゃまなんだ…よ。
You ass! You're in my way! Oh?
ハァ？
あぁ？
また出た～！
なんで～！
More of 'em!
But why?!
うわ～ん！チキショー！
ヤケクソだ～！
Damn it! I don't care anymore!
D-Don't hurt me!
≪助けて～！≫≪あ～！≫
あ～…。
…ったく　何なんだ
人をバケモノみたいに。
What was with them?!
Treating us like we're monsters or something.
男鹿？
ん？よお！
Oga?
Yo.
それに東条も。
And Tojo too?
ああ？おめえら何で
そんなカッコしてんだ？
What're you all wearing that getup for?
ちょっと　色々事情があったのよ！
Uh, you know! It's a really long story.
そっちこそ　今まで
どこ行ってたの？
But you guys! Where have
you been all this time?
メシ食ってた。メシ作ってた。
ダダダ…。
I had food.
I made food.
あぁ？
神崎　姫川と夏目もいるわね。
Kanzaki? Himekawa and
Natsume are over there too.
いて　わりぃかよ。
（姫川）ヤァ。
どうも。
Something wrong with bein' here?
Yo.
Greetings.
う…ぐ…。
見てろぉ　ここには何十人も
仲間が来てんだ。
Just you wait!
I got dozens of mates right here!
あいつら　まとめて…。
If we all ganged up and...
By, "mates," could you mean these?
（七海）お仲間って
これのことかしら？
この学園で
好き勝手は　させませんよ。
We don't allow willful
violence at this school.
同意。
Agreed.
ろ　六騎聖まで…。
こうなったら　あの人を。ヒッ！→
E-Even the 6 Holy Knights...?
My last resort! I'll call...
痛いよ～　助けて！痛いよ～！
It hurts! Please spare me! Oh, the pain!
Now, it seems we're all here.
さて　全員おそろいのようね。
そろそろ試合の時間よ。
The time for our match is fast approaching.
ええ。
（三木）≪男鹿≫
あ？
Yeah.
Oga.
You're late.
（三木）遅かったじゃないか。楽しみにしてな。→
I'm lookin' forward to this! So much that I
came up with an ultimate, never-fail attack.
超絶新必殺技が完成したぜ。
ふ～ん。
（霧矢）フフ…。
いや～古市さん！何だね山村くん！
Hey, Furuichi-san!
What is it, Yamamura-kun?
すごかったっスね～！まさか試合前に→
Wasn't that amazing?
Nobody would've thought the TKKH and the 6
Holy Knights would both muster before the game!
東邦神姫と六騎聖の
勢ぞろいが見られるなんて！
ハッハッハッ！まあな。
さて　それじゃ　オレも試合に…。→
True, I suppose.
Now, I too must be off to the game...
あ？っと…どうせ　また
アランドロンのオッサンだろ？
I know who you are. You're
old man Alaindelon, right?
いつものオチで
見え見えなんだよな…。あら？
I see you every day in my own house...
Huh?
ウフッ！
おぉ～っ！何なになに？→
Oh? What can this be?!
試合前に　はげましのエールで
送ってくれるのかな？
Are you here to give me a
cheer before my big game?
アハハ…。
あんたのせいで　結局
メチャクチャになったじゃないの！
Our whole café is broken to
pieces, and it's all your fault!
What'll you do to make up for it?!
ど～してくれんのよっ！！
えぇ～っ！そんなぁ。
Nooo!
Um... Can we...
えっと　その…。
う～っ！ウッ…。
ご主人様　ガンバ！あら？（古市）ウゥッ…。
Master? Hang in there!
Oh?
It can be hard!
It can be sad!
But in this coat, how can I cry?
Don't cry!
(Attack!)
Your singing doesn't help either!
On the next Beelzebub: Time
for the Game to Begin!
But I can't hold back the tears!
Yes, you are moved to tears!
After all, he's just a ghoul!
I told you not to cry, didn't I?!
(Attack!)
On this court, there's a demon living inside!